You can't drink or eat
until the anesthesia wears off.
Print out the report.
The self-service printer is over there.
Do you want to eat something now?
I'll get you
some light porridge.
I want to have my blood drawn for tests.
What should I do?
Zhou Yang
didn't lie to us.
I guess
he was attacked by Fu Binyan's
sharp tongue,
and woke up.
I'll tell everyone
in the group.
Tonight,
everyone can rest assured.
I hope Zhou Yang
can rely on us more in the future.
I also sent a training plan
for the Middle School Affiliated
to the group.
If you want to be relied on,
don't just talk about it.
Train hard from now on.
Gu Chenyang,
you're a real devil.
Let's go.
Mom,
You're still in the suburbs?
Are you busy?
Not too much. How about you?
How are you doing today?
Have you eaten yet?
Yes.
What did you eat?
Porridge. I had porridge.
And some bread and cookies.
Pretty good.
Porridge? Why would you eat porridge?
Are you feeling unwell?
No.
I just...
I...
Do you think this is being sensible?
This is being foolish.
Sometimes,
you have to be willing to bother others.
Otherwise,
you will make the people who care about you
feel sad.
Yangyang.
Did you hear me?
Mom.
I was hospitalized for low blood sugar.
Yangyang.
Mom.
You're here.
What happened?
Why are you in the hospital?
Come here.
Lie down. Don't get up.
What happened to you?
Do you have a fever?
No.
Then where
do you feel uncomfortable?
I'm fine now.
You've been injected, right?
What's going on?
How did you get hypoglycemia?
Did you
skip meals again?
How did it get so serious?
I'm sorry, mom.
You're so busy with work,
and I'm still like this.
Don't say sorry to me.
How could you even think about
to hide it from me.
Do you think you can hide it?
Yang,
do you think
I only care about work
and not you?
Mom,
it's just low blood sugar.
It's not that serious.
How is it not serious?
Let me tell you, low blood sugar
can be life-threatening.
If something happened to you,
what would I do?
I would regret it for the rest of my life.
Mom, don't cry.
Yang, I know
you don't want to burden me,
so you didn't tell me.
But do you remember
the last time
I had appendicitis,
when I had appendicitis?
That's what I should do.
There's no such thing.
You're a kid.
I should take care of you.
I just called
your class teacher on the way here.
I just knew
how busy
and tired
you were at school.
Yang,
it's my fault.
I've been
too busy with work
and didn't take care of you.
But you can't just
hide everything from me.
I'm sorry, mom.
I was wrong.
I was wrong, Yang.
I really was wrong this time.
I'm sorry. I apologize.
Mom.
I know
you're a sensible boy.
But sometimes,
I really don't want you to be so sensible.
Do you remember
what I told you
when I got divorced?
You said
the two of us
we're a team.
Yeah, what does that mean?
It means we face things
together,
we work together,
and we make life
beautiful together.
But the key
is that both of us
have to take care of ourselves
so we can rely on each other.
Got it?
I'll change, Mom.
You don't need to change.
You're doing great already.
Remember,
we have to work together.
Okay.
Mom,
can I give you a hug?
Come here.
Whatever happens in the future,
you must tell me.
Got it?
Got it, mom.
Down, down, down!
Did you guys
understand the tactics I just explained?
Coach,
actually, Zhou Yang understood them,
and then he explained to us.
Fine,
go watch the video
and review it.
Okay.
Zhou Yang's not here.
Are you worried too?
I always thought
I had everything
under control,
but now I realize
he was handling a lot of the details.
Alright.
Stop overthinking.
Get some rest.
Do you know how to do this?
I don't know either.
It took you so long to find a first-aid kit.
It hurts so much.
If you had come later,
my wound would have healed.
Zhou Yang used to manage the first-aid kit.
It took me a long time to find it.
Why is the spray gone?
Chi Jia,
are you trying to kill me?
Stop it.
I'll look for it again.
This is not right.
Press this button.
Is it done?
Oh, no.
What's wrong?
Only three seconds were recorded.
The storage card is full.
Coach Su wants us to review.
My layup was in vain.
Xu Anbo,
didn't I tell you to keep an eye on it?
I need to train too.
Besides,
Zhou Yang usually
takes care of the storage card.
Zhou Yang, I miss you.
I miss you too.
Me too.
What are you...
Without him,
are you going to fall apart?
The more you practice, the better you get.
Don't you get it?
That's more like it.
I was starting to think someone swapped you out.
Just be yourself.
Come on.
Listen to my tactics.
Mom,
I'll be ready soon.
It's okay.
Don't rush.
I'll wait for you.
What are you doing?
Happy discharge.
Happy every day.
Good health.
Blow out the candles.
It's boring.
Take it.
Thank you.
Where is Xu Anbo?
Xu Anbo
has something to deal with at home.
He asked us to tell you
to return to the team as soon as possible.
We all need you.
Yes.
But
we also
made a decision today.
We'll take care of
the trivial matters
of the team.
We won't let you
bear it alone anymore.
Even if you want to,
we won't let you.
By the way,
I have a decision
to tell you.
I used to
think I could handle
everything on my own.
But from now on,
I won't do
everything myself.
We are a team.
We should share the burden together.
That's right.
From now on, we all
should carry it together.
Okay.
Right.
From now on, we should share the burden together.
Fu Binyan.
Don't touch me.
Yangyang.
Hello, auntie.
Hello.
What do you want to eat?
I'll make it for you when we get back.
Okay.
What's wrong, Zhou Yang?
Why are you laughing?
Nothing.
I just feel
very happy.
We will always
be by your side.
Thank you for coming
to pick Zhou Yang up from the hospital.
Thank you.
Auntie,
it's what we should do.
Where's Fu Binyan?
He went to the bathroom.
You guys go ahead.
I'll wait for him.
Okay, go ahead.
Let's go.
Dr. Qin,
has the physical examination report come out?
I want to know
the current situation
of my heart disease.
Is it still possible
for me to play basketball?
Heart disease?
Okay, I see.
I'll keep that in mind.
Did you hear all that?
Don't tell Zhou Yang.
Don't tell anyone.
I swear to God,
I won't tell anyone.
So,
you're not joining the basketball club
because you look down on us,
but because of your health.
Why are you laughing?
Nothing.
Although it may be
a little unkind,
I'm still very happy.
Do you actually
want to join us very much?
Slow down.
Coach
I'm back.
Welcome.
You can't do this again.
If you don't feel well,
you can't just push through.
Your body
doesn't just belong to you,
it also belongs to the team.
Got it?
Yes, sir.
I won't do it again.
Sit down.
Now,
let's get down to business.
The group stage
consists of six games.
We've played three.
Yibei
has one win and two losses,
putting us at the bottom of the standings.
But there's still a chance.
So, the next game
against the Middle School Affiliated to the Institute of Physical Education,
we must win.
You know,
The Sports Institute's Middle School is a top team.
With your previous
scattered and uncoordinated style of play,
you definitely can't win.
So you have to master
the tactical system I've set up.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
I have another piece of news.
The Middle School Affiliated to the Institute of Physical Education
has a new player this year.
He is very strong.
He may become
a big obstacle to your victory.
Who is he?
I don't know.
The Middle School Affiliated to the Institute of Physical Education
is good at teamwork.
Now,
they have an ace up their sleeve.
It's even harder to beat them.
Oh my god.
It's like a mission impossible.
What kind of player?
What's his name?
What does he look like?
His name is Xie Yizhou.
He has never
played a single public game.
But he has a nickname,
Stats Monster.
What?
What does it mean?
It means that
his data in all aspects of technology
are insanely high.
Just like cheating in games.
He is a basketball genius.
A genius.
Did you hear that?
So,
next,
you all need to
follow my guidance
and carry it out to the end.
Because only a genius
can defeat a genius.
Coach,
we don't have any geniuses here.
I, the 1.87-meter genius,
am standing right here.
Can't you see?
Are you talking about yourself?
Didn't I convince you
in that one-on-one?
Want to try again?
No, no, no.
No need.
I'm convinced, I'm convinced.
That's more like it.
But coach,
shouldn't we
learn more about the player
to better handle the game?
Fu Binyan,
do you have more information on him?
No.
Then how can that be?
We need a game guide.
I, the genius coach,
have already planned everything for you.
What?
This is what you and the coach
came up with?
Sneaking into their school to spy?
Don't put it that way,
okay?
This is called on-the-ground research,
understand?
Got it, totally.
Sounds super exciting.
What if we get caught?
Don't worry,
I'm all set.
Where did you get the uniforms?
Getting a few uniforms
is a piece of cake for me.
That's so you, Connections Guy.
Impressive.
Let's go.
Let's find a place to change clothes first,
then we can go in.
What's up?
Gu Chenyang,
are you scared?
If you don't go in,
the training will be over soon.
Reverse psychology doesn't work on me.
Fine.
Then if we lose the next game,
the basketball club will be disbanded,
Then I can go back
and continue my band.
Let's make a deal.
Don't run around when you get in.
Just watch quietly for a while and leave.
No problem.
Okay.
Just this time.
Let's go.
Nice.
Backboard!
Behind you!
Good!
Defense, defense!
Go!
Just sit here.
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
Be careful.
It's okay.
Look at that tall guy.
My source said
he seems to be
the newcomer a few days ago.
He should be Xie Yizhou.
Oh my god.
He's so strong.
If I was bumped by him,
I would fly away.
Oh my god.
Something is wrong.
This person
is outstanding in physical conditions,
he is not flexible enough.
And he lacks communication with his teammates.
The Middle School Affiliated to the Institute of Physical Education always emphasizes
teamwork.
The main players should not be like this.
What should we do?
How about we ask someone?
Who?
Why does that person's back look so...
You guys,
What are you doing taking pictures with your phone?
What are you doing sneaking around here?
Which class are you from?
We are...
Don't say that.
Go, run.
Quick, go.
Go see what's going on.
Stop.
Don't run.
Stop!
You fools!
Oh no!
Come in!
Hurry up!
Where are they?
They're not here.
No?
Let's check over there.
Go.
They're gone.
Thank you,
for your help.
It's okay.
Why were they chasing you?
Probably from the Yibei team.
They look serious.
Who are you?
From the basketball team?
I just watch your games often.
Don't be nervous.
If I wanted to expose you,
I wouldn't have helped you
just now.
Gu Chenyang,
your three-pointers are awesome.
You really know him?
We've lost twice in a row,
but we still have fans.
The results don't represent our strength.
Li Haoyu
is good at quick breakthroughs.
Lin Qingyuan,
you have a high shooting accuracy.
You practice every day, right?
Thanks to Gu Chenyang
for designing it for me.
You just called us seniors.
Are you a middle school student?
Yeah, I'm in the 9th grade,
at the middle school here.
Have you heard of
the basketball team's prodigy?
We came here specially to...
It's getting late.
Thank you for your help.
We have to go now.
You're leaving already?
I can show you around.
No need.
We have other things to do.
Let's go.
Goodbye.
Thank you.
See you next time. Bye.
Goodbye.